//General questions
let questionsLevel1 = [
    {
        question: "Which is the main color of the Simpsons world?",
        options: ["Blue", "Green", "Yellow", "Pink"],
        answer: "Yellow"
    },
    {
        question: "How many kids are there in the Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Four", "Five", "Seven", "Three"],
        answer: "Three"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the simpsons' neighbour?",
        options: ["Milhouse", "Carl", "Moe", "Flanders"],
        answer: "Flanders"
    },
    {
        question: "Where does Homer work?",
        options: ["Nuclear Power Plant", "Moe's Bar", "Kwik-E-Mart", "Hospital"],
        answer: "Nuclear Power Plant"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Springfield's Police Chief?",
        options: ["Chief Raplh", "Chief Flanders", "Chief Homer", "Chief Wiggum"],
        answer: "Chief Wiggum"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Springfield's Mayor?",
        options: ["Quimby", "Ralph", "Wiggum", "Brockman"],
        answer: "Quimby"
    },
    {
        question: "Where do The Simpsons live?",
        options: ["Quahog", "Cleveland", "Springfield", "Langley Falls"],
        answer: "Springfield"
    }
]

//Questions about the family member's names
let questionsLevel2 = [
    {
        question: "What is the father's name in The Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Mr. Burns", "Bart", "Homer", "Carl"],
        answer: "Homer"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mother's name in The Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Lisa", "Edna", "Patty", "Marge"],
        answer: "Marge"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the son's name in The Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Bart", "Ned", "Moe", "Apu"],
        answer: "Bart"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the older daughter's name in The Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Lisa", "Maude", "Selma", "Marge"],
        answer: "Lisa"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the baby's name in The Simpsons family?",
        options: ["Lisa", "Patty", "Maggie", "Marge"],
        answer: "Maggie"
    }
]

//Questions about Homer
let questionsLevel3 = [
    {
        question: "What is Homer's favourite beer?",
        options: ["Bud", "Pawtucket", "Heineken", "Duff"],
        answer: "Duff"
    },
    {
        question: "How many hairs does Homer have?",
        options: ["Fully haired", "Two", "Three", "He is bald"],
        answer: "Two"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the color of Homer's pants?",
        options: ["Blue", "White", "Green", "Black"],
        answer: "Blue"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Homer's wife?",
        options: ["Lisa", "Maude", "Selma", "Marge"],
        answer: "Marge"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Homer frequently steal from his neighbour?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about Lisa
let questionsLevel4 = [
    {
        question: "What is Lisa's favourite musical instrument?",
        options: ["Saxophone", "Trumpet", "Bandolin", "Guitar"],
        answer: "Saxophone"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the color of Lisa's dress?",
        options: ["Orange", "White", "Green", "Black"],
        answer: "Orange"
    },
    {
        question: "Lisa is ...",
        options: ["Older than Homer", "Older than Maggie", "Older than Marge", "Older than Bart"],
        answer: "Older than Maggie"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Lisa's brother?",
        options: ["Apu", "Ralph", "Bart", "Milhouse"],
        answer: "Bart"
    },
    {
        question: "Is Lisa not a vegatarian?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "No"
    },
    {
        question: "Besides English what other language does Lisa speak?",
        options: ["Italian", "German", "French", "Spanish"],
        answer: "Italian"
    }
]

//Questions about Bart
let questionsLevel5 = [
    {
        question: "What is the color of Bart's shorts?",
        options: ["White", "Yellow", "Blue", "Green"],
        answer: "Blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Bart's best friend?",
        options: ["Homer", "Ralph", "Carl", "Milhouse"],
        answer: "Milhouse"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Bart's father?",
        options: ["Homer", "Carl", "Moe", "Skinner"],
        answer: "Homer"
    },
    {
        question: "The person who does is male or female?",
        options: ["Male", "Female"],
        answer: "Female"
    },
    {
        question: "Which piece of clothes Bart is always telling people to eat?",
        options: ["Jeans", "Pants", "Shorts", "Trunks"],
        answer: "Shorts"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Bart's real name?",
        options: ["Homero", "Bartholomew", "Bartino", "Ambar"],
        answer: "Bartholomew"
    }
]

//Questions about Marge
let questionsLevel6 = [
    {
        question: "What is the color of Marge's hair?",
        options: ["White", "Yellow", "Blue", "Green"],
        answer: "Blue"
    },
    {
        question: "Which are the names of Marge's children?",
        options: ["Maggie, Lisa and Mr. Burns", "Bart, Lisa and Maggie", "Bart, Lisa and Moe", "Milhouse, Bart and Lisa"],
        answer: "Bart, Lisa and Maggie"
    },
    {
        question: "Is Homer Marge's husband?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "How many sisters does Marge have?",
        options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
        answer: "Two"
    },
    {
        question: "Marge's sisters are not twins?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "No"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Marge commit any crime during the show?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about Maggie
let questionsLevel7 = [
    {
        question: "Which are the name of Maggie's parents?",
        options: ["Homer and Marge", "Homer and Selma", "Carl and Marge", "Moe and Marge"],
        answer: "Homer and Marge"
    },
    {
        question: "Which other character has the same hair shape as Maggie?",
        options: ["Milhouse", "Lisa", "Homer", "Marge"],
        answer: "Lisa"
    },
]

//Questions related to Bart's friends 
let questionsLevel8 = [
    {
        question: "Is Milhouse considered Bart's best friend?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Bart's bully in the show?",
        options: ["Homer", "Nelson", "Milhouse", "Moe"],
        answer: "Nelson"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is Bart's nemesis?",
        options: ["Duffman", "Sideshow Mel", "Krusty The Clown", "Sideshow Bob"],
        answer: "Sideshow Bob"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Milhouse were glasses?",
        options: ["No", "Yes"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Nelson were glasses?",
        options: ["No", "Yes"],
        answer: "No"
    },
    {
        question: "Are Milhouse's parents still married?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "No"
    }
]

//Questions about Flanders
let questionsLevel9 = [
    {
        question: "Which is Flander's religion?",
        options: ["Muslemism", "Judaism", "Christianism", "Buddhism"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Flanders have a mustache?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "How many children does Flanders have?",
        options: ["Two", "Three", "Six", "One"],
        answer: "Two"
    },
    {
        question: "Is Flanders a religious man?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about characters related to Moe's bar
let questionsLevel10 = [
    {
        question: "What is the name of Homer's favourite bar?",
        options: ["Drunken Clam", "Moe's", "Cheers","Oneil's"],
        answer: "Moe's"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the owner of Homer's favourite bar?",
        options: ["Carl", "Barney", "Lenny", "Moe"],
        answer: "Moe"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Homer usually drink at Moe's?",
        options: ["Vodka", "Beer", "Water", "Wine"],
        answer: "Beer"
    },
    {
        question: "With who does Homer usually spend his time at Moe's?",
        options: ["Lisa and Bart", "Lenny and Carl", "Moe and Lenny", "Carl and Moe"],
        answer: "Lenny and Carl"
    }
]

//Questions about Krusty
let questionsLevel11 = [
    {
        question: "Who is Krusty?",
        options: ["The Clown", "The SideShow Krusty", "The Principal","The Comic Book Guy"],
        answer: "The Clown"
    },
    {
        question: "Does Krusty have a TV Show?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about Comic Book Guy
let questionsLevel12 = [
    {
        question: "The Comic Book Guy sells two items in his store, which are they?",
        options: ["Gum, baseball cards and comic books", "Baseball Cards and gum", "Comic books and baseball cards","Comic books and gum"],
        answer: "Comic books and baseball cards"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these describes the Comic Book Guy's physical appearance?",
        options: ["Obese", "Slim", "Muscular", "Crippled"],
        answer: "Obese"
    },
    {
        question: "Is the Comic Book Guy considered a geek?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about Ralph Wiggum
let questionsLevel13 = [
    {
        question: "Who is Ralph Wiggum's father?",
        options: ["Homer Wiggum", "Chief Wiggum", "Kent Wiggum", "Groundskeeper Wiggum"],
        answer: "Chief Wiggum"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Raplh Wiggum always picking?",
        options: ["His elbow", "His hear", "His nose", "His neck"],
        answer: "His nose"
    },
    {
        question: "Is Ralph Wiggum considered smart?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "No"
    }
]

//Questions about Aliens, Kang and Kodos
let questionsLevel14 = [
    {
        question: "Are there aliens in The Simpsons?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the aliens' color the The Simpson?",
        options: ["Orange", "Black", "Blue", "Green"],
        answer: "Green"
    }
]

//Questions about Otto
let questionsLevel15 = [
    {
        question: "Which vehicle Otto drives for Springfield Elementary?",
        options: ["Car", "Bus", "Motorbike","Truck"],
        answer: "Bus"
    },
    {
        question: "Which is Otto's favourite music genre?",
        options: ["Heavy Metal", "Rock", "Pop", "Reggae"],
        answer: "Heavy Metal"
    },
    {
        question: "Otto usually treats people by Dude?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "Have there been signs during the show that Otto does drugs?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "Yes"
    }
]

//Questions about other characters
let questionsLevel16 = [
    {
        question: "What does Mr. Burns own?",
        options: ["Nuclear Power Plant", "Kwik-E-Mart", "Comic Book Store", "Bar"],
        answer: "Nuclear Power Plant"
    },
    {
        question: "Who owns Kwik-E-Mart?",
        options: ["Flanders", "Apu", "Homer", "Moe"],
        answer: "Apu"
    },
    {
        question: "Where is Groundskeeper Willie from?",
        options: ["Ireland", "Portugal", "Netherlands", "Germany"],
        answer: "Ireland"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the character that has a bone stuck in his hair?",
        options: ["SideShow Bob", "SideShow Mel", "Kent Brockman", "Mayor Quimby"],
        answer: "SideShow Mel"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Kent Brockman?",
        options: ["TV host", "Priest", "Mayor", "Doctor"],
        answer: "TV host"
    }
]

//Questions about the show's generic
let questionsLevel17 = [
    {
        question: "Where does the Simpsons family sit at the end of every generic?",
        options: ["On the floor", "On their couch", "On the stairs", "In separate rooms"],
        answer: "On their couch"
    },
    {
        question: "In the generic Homer is ran over by who?",
        options: ["Marge", "Bart", "Lisa", "Maggie"],
        answer: "Marge"
    },
    {
        question: "Is the generic the same on very The Simpsons episode?",
        options: ["Yes", "No"],
        answer: "No"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is in detention at the beginning of every episode?",
        options: ["Marge", "Bart", "Lisa", "Maggie"],
        answer: "Bart"
    },
    {
        question: "In the generice, who is sitting in the car with Marge?",
        options: ["Marge", "Bart", "Lisa", "Maggie"],
        answer: "Maggie"
    }
]

//Questions about Simpsons The Movie
let questionsLevel18 = [
    {
        question: "Which animal is Homer's new pet on Simpsons The Movie?",
        options: ["Dog", "Horse", "Cat", "Pig"],
        answer: "Pig"
    },
    {
        question: "Which animal gets extra eyes after being exposed to radioactive matter in Simpsons The Movie?",
        options: ["Dog", "Bird", "Fish", "Pig"],
        answer: "Fish"
    },
    {
        question: "Which famous band stars in Simpsons The Movie?",
        options: ["Coldplay", "Nirvana", "U2", "Green Day"],
        answer: "Green Day"
    },
    {
        question: "Who causes the pollution crisis in Simpsons The Movie?",
        options: ["Otto", "Marge", "Chief Wiggum", "Homer"],
        answer: "Homer"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Homer throw into a lake that causes the pollution crisis in Simpsons The Movie?",
        options: ["Car", "Silo", "Garbage", "Microwave"],
        answer: "Silo"
    }
]

//Questions about characters famous quotes
let questionsLevel19 = [
    {
        question: "Who says...`D'oh!`?",
        options: ["Homer Simpson", "Bart Simpson", "Maggie Simpson", "Marge Simpson"],
        answer: "Homer Simpson"
    },
    {
        question: "Who says...`Ay Caramba!`?",
        options: ["Homer Simpson", "Bart Simpson", "Maggie Simpson", "Marge Simpson"],
        answer: "Bart Simpson"
    },
    {
        question: "Who says...`Stupid Flanders!`?",
        options: ["Homer Simpson", "Bart Simpson", "Maggie Simpson", "Marge Simpson"],
        answer: "Homer Simpson"
    },
    {
        question: "Who says...`It tastes like…burning!`?",
        options: ["Nelson Muntz", "Bart Simpson", "Milhouse Van Houten", "Ralph Wiggum"],
        answer: "Ralph Wiggum"
    },
    {
        question: "Who says...`Ha Ha!`?",
        options: ["Nelson Muntz", "Bart Simpson", "Milhouse Van Houten", "Ralph Wiggum"],
        answer: "Nelson Muntz"
    },

]

//Questions about characters famous quotes
let questionsLevel20 = [
    {
        question: "Which year was the first episode of The Simpson broadcast?",
        options: ["1989", "1945", "2011", "1992"],
        answer: "1989"
    }
]